[Mark] So Sady graduated with a degree in digital
cinematography. But not only did she
graduate with a degree in digital
cinematography, she graduated as one of
the top members of her class.
[Applause]
In fact, she got the advanced achievement
award. Now the beautiful thing about it
was is this was an online course, and
because it was an online course, no one
on the other end knew that she had a
disability. All they saw was her ability.
Not even her professors knew that she
had a disability. All they were able to
see was the extreme talent and this
artist with an amazing amount of ability.
[Applause]
[Sady] Technology is a huge part of my life.
I use it daily. It's part of my DNA.
I have every device you can think of:
an Apple watch; three computers; an iPhone;
an iPad; an Apple TV; and everything in
between. But these devices alone are not
what empowers me —  it is what is being
built into these devices that empower
and enable me to access my world, my
dreams, and my inner artist. Accessibility
features such as switch control and
text-to-speech. Switch control gives me
full access to my devices. Text-to-speech
gives me my voice.  [Mark] We really live in an
amazing time because a lot of the
assistive technologies and accessibility
features that are built into our devices
are available to all learners. Everyone.
It levels that playing field. It really
provides accessibility to a wide range
of users all over. But to me, it's really
more than accessibility. It's accessing
abilities. It's about finding those tools
that will allow artists to explore the
inner artist within and to become the
talented professionals like Sady.
[Sady] If you're seeing me through the lens of my
disability, it's not okay but I
understand. It's human nature, but don't
feel sorry for me. I am here to help
change the narrative —  to change the
perception — to tear down barriers and to
give you a different lens which to see
me through. I will not do it by lecturing
people. I will show you by being an
example. By telling stories through video
and with video. So I ask you to see
beyond my disability and see my ability.
See me as the intelligent, passionate, and
independent woman I am. See the artist
within. [Mark] Thank you!